



Key skills

- SQL
- Database Testing
- Integration Testing
- Web Testing
- Functional Testing
- · Bug Life Cycle
- Test Strategy
- · Anti Money Laundering
- JIRA Tool
- Manual Functional Testing
- Agile Methodology
- Azure DevOps
- · Payment Processing
- Tableau
- · Scrum Development



Languages

- English
- Hindi



Social links

https://in.linkedin.com/in/prakhar-chourey-971ba5112

Prakhar Chourey

Test Team Lead



9 Years 0 Month



+91) 9599490055

prakhar.jb007@gmail.c



Profile Summary

Looking for an opportunity to serve my family, organisation with the best of my abilities. "Keen to enhance my knowledge and utilize my skills for the betterment of the firm and myself". Enthusiastic, determined, go-geter and cordial are among my defining qualities.

I have 8+ years of relevent experience in Testing and QA Process.



Education

B.Tech/B.E., 2015

Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal



Work Experience

Mar 2021 - Present

Test Team Lead

Accenture Operation Solution

I have hands on experience in Quality assurance, Manual/Automation Testing, SQL, Database testing, ETL Testing, Agile. Gained good understanding on ISO, CHAPS, Wire transfers, Target2, Euro1 etc clearings

May 2020 - Mar 2021

Validation Analyst

Bioclinica

Worked as Validation Analyst in CTMS(Clinical Trials Management system). Gained experience in Manual Functional testing of Clinical Trials and Pharma. Worked on test management tools like Azure DevOps, SharePoint etc.

Jun 2018 - Feb 2020

Quality Analyst

Fiserv

Worked as QA Associate for almost 2 years on Anti-money laundering project and gained good knowledge in tools like TFS,MTM, Agilescrum.

Jun 2015 - May 2018

Senior Setup Configuration Specialist

Alight Solutions

Joined Alight in June-2015, as intern and later on promoted to Sr. Setup configuration specialist. Worked on SQL, tools like Maestro, Total benefits administrator etc.



Projects

214 Days

Clinical Trial Management System V-3.8

Working as a Validation Analyst for BIOCLINIC in CTMS project.

304 Days

Anti Money Laundering Product FCRM

FCRM is abbreviation of Financial crime and risk management and is an Anti money laundering tool, which many banks across the world use.

61 Days

Data Audit

Cleanup of Bad data present in production database, writing SQL queries, running and monitoring batch jobs for fetching the reports from database.

151 Days

WEB And GUI TESTING

Web testing, Regression Testing and System testing under SDLC process.

30 Months

ISO migration for MT, CAMT, PACS msgs for clearings like Target2, Euro1, HKISO, FED, WTX etc.

I am part of project which is an ongoing massive change in payments domain, where All the conventional MT messages are migrated to readable XML(MX) format.



Certification

- · Certified scrum master (CSM)
- Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO)